sneakermaniac.com 2016-06-05

# Privacy Policy |

Thank you for visiting EQUNIU.com. YOU SHOULD READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. These Legal Conditions govern the use of and access to this website (www.equniu.com and EQUNIU).

Your use of this Site is governed by the following terms of use (Terms). If you do not agree with all of these Terms, exit this Site. By using this Site, you agree to comply with and to be bound by these Terms, including the privacy policy and, when you make an online purchase, the purchase information. **EQUNIU.com** reserves the right to, from time to time, change these Terms at its sole discretion. By using this Site after any such change, you agree to comply with, and be bound by, the Terms as changed.

**Cookies & What’s collected  
**

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used and revised from time to time. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

_1\. Log Files_

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

_2\. Cookies_

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, EQUNIU has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites. Google, a third party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads on EQUNIU. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google’s Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

**Links**

This site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for the operation of or content located on or through any such site. By reading this you comply and will not hold EQUNIU.com liable for any actions made through those such sites.

**Category:**

Thank you for visiting EQUNIU.com. YOU SHOULD READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. These Legal Conditions govern the use of and access to this website (www.equniu.com and EQUNIU).

Your use of this Site is governed by the following terms of use (Terms). If you do not agree with all of these Terms, exit this Site. By using this Site, you agree to comply with and to be bound by these Terms, including the privacy policy and, when you make an online purchase, the purchase information. **EQUNIU.com** reserves the right to, from time to time, change these Terms at its sole discretion. By using this Site after any such change, you agree to comply with, and be bound by, the Terms as changed.

**Cookies & What’s collected  
**

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used and revised from time to time. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

_1\. Log Files_

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

_2\. Cookies_

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, EQUNIU has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites. Google, a third party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads on EQUNIU. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google’s Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

**Links**

This site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for the operation of or content located on or through any such site. By reading this you comply and will not hold EQUNIU.com liable for any actions made through those such sites.

**Category:**
